莉莉丝正在试图打破这66个封印
Lilith is trying to break the 66 seals
把路西法从地狱里释放出来
To free lucifer from hell.
路西法将带来天启
Lucifer will bring the apocalypse.
你占据了某个混蛋的身体?
You're possessing some poor bastard?
这只是一具皮囊而已
This is...a vessel.
我同意占据他的灵魂
I had to give my consent to invite him in.
恰克 雪莉?
Chuck shurley?
我们的生活已经被你写进你的书里了
We have a life. you've been using it to write your books.
迪恩  让他走  这个人是被庇护的
Dean,let him go. this man is to be protected.
为什么? 他是主的先知
Why? he's a prophet of the lord.
-你是谁？- 我是撒迦利亚  卡西迪奥的上司
- Who are you? - I'm zachariah. I'm castiel's superior.
-我要怎么去干掉莉莉丝？- 没你什么事了
- And how am I gonna ice lilith? - You're not.
莉莉丝正要去打破最后一个封印
Lilith's going to break the final seal.
你不想去阻止天启，是么？
You don't want to stop it,do you?
你是上帝选中的  你要去阻止它
You are chosen. you will stop it.
只是不是莉莉丝或者天启  就这样
Just...not lilith or the apocalypse,that's all.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
-萨姆  我们走  - 迪恩
Sammy,let's go. - Dean...
他要来了
He's coming.
快跑
Come on.
迪恩
Dean!
你叫什么鬼名字?
What the devil is your name?
约塞米蒂 萨姆
Yo...yosemite sam!
约塞米蒂 萨姆?
Yosemite sam?
让我来看看
Hmm,let's see.
萨姆
Sam...
在这儿
Ah,here it is.
怎么回事?
What the hell?
我不知道
I don't know.
各位旅客  这是飞行简短播报
Folks,quick word from the flight deck.
我们刚飞过伊尔切斯特  然后是埃利科特城
We're just passing over ilchester,then ellicott city,
我们将先降落在巴尔的摩
On our initial descent into baltimore...
伊尔切斯特？我们刚才不是在那里？
Ilchester? weren't we just there?
如果你愿意去散步
So if you'd like to stretch your legs,
现在会是好时机
Now would be a good time to --
我靠!
Holy crap!
州长欧玛丽呼吁民众保持冷静
...and governor o'malley urged calm,
表示恐怖份子把一座废弃的修道院
Saying it's very unlikely an abandoned convent
作为目标另人难以置信
Would be a target for terrorists,
- 无论国外还是国内  - 换台
- Either foreign or homegrown. - Change the station.
飓风金利
Announcer #2: hurricane kinley,
突然猛烈登陆加尔维斯顿地区
Unexpectedly slamming into the galveston area...
宣布了北朝鲜核试验成功
Announcer #3: ...announced a successful test of the north korean nuclear...
- 困惑  - 猪流感
- Announcer #4: ...baffled... - Announcer #5: ...swine flu...
迪恩
Dean --
别  什么都别说
Don't...don't say anything.
会没事的
It's okay.
我们只要保持冷静
We just got to keep our heads down
先敲定这个  好么?
And hash this out,all right?
对 没错
Yeah,okay.
很好  重要的事情先来
All right,well,first things first --
我们是如何最后上了"灵魂飞机"?
How did we end up on "soul plane"?
也许是天使们?
Angels,maybe?
我的意思是 带我们走出险境
I mean,you know,beaming us out of harm's way?
无论如何  这是我们最担心的
Well,whatever. it's the least of our worries.
我们要找到卡西
We need to find cass.
萨姆
Sam.
你好啊 恰克
Yeah! hey,chuck.
你没事吧?
So... you're okay?
头被你砸了
Well,my head hurts.
不  我的意思是 我最后的幻像
No,I mean -- I mean,my -- my last vision.
你看上像装了新款的马达
You went,like,full-on vader.
你体温150度  你的心率200
Your body temperature was 150. your heart rate was 200.
你的眼睛是黑的
Your eyes were black.
你的眼睛变黑了?
Your eyes went black?
我不清楚
I didn't know.
卡西在哪
Where's cass?
他挂了
He's dead.
或被驱逐了
Or gone.
大天使放弃了他
The archangel smote the crap out of him.
我很抱歉  你肯定么？
I'm sorry. you're sure?
我的意思是也许他只是在光芒或是什么东西中消失了
I mean,maybe he just vanished into the light or something.
不  他像是被打爆了
Oh,no. he,like,exploded.
像个肥皂泡球
Like a water balloon of chunky soup.
你有一个
You got a...
在这里?
Uh...right here?
上帝
Oh,god.
那是一颗臼齿
Is that a molar?
我头发里怎么会有一颗臼齿?
Do I have a molar in my hair?
真是非常操蛋的一天
This has been a really stressful day.
卡西  你这个蠢蛋
Cass,you stupid bastard.
蠢?他以前试着帮助我们
Stupid? he was trying to help us.
确实如此
Yeah,exactly.
现在怎样？我不知道
So,what now? I don't know.
我的老天
Oh,crap.
什么?
What?
我能感觉他们
I can feel them.
感觉我们会找到你这里
Thought we'd find you here.
游戏时间结束  迪恩
Playtime's over,dean.
是时候和我们一起了
Time to come with us.
你只要保持距离  傻帽
You just keep your distance,ass-hat.
你很烦恼
You're upset.
有一点儿
Yeah -- a little.
你不要脸的发动审判日
You sons of bitches jump-started judgment day!
也许我们该让它发生  我们不启动任何东西
Maybe we let it happen. we didn't start anything.
对吗  萨姆？
Right,sammy?
你有一个机会阻止你兄弟  但你没有
You had a chance to stop your brother,and you couldn't.
因此  我们不要纠缠谁开始什么
So let's not quibble over who started what.
我们只说我们的缺点  然后前进
Let's just say it was all our faults and move on.
不管你喜欢不喜欢
'cause like it or not...
现在是天启了
...it's apocalypse now.
我们要再次回归同一队来
And we're back on the same team again.
是这样么?
Is that so?
你想杀死恶魔  我们需要你杀死恶魔
You want to kill the devil. we want you to kill the devil.
这是合作
It's...synergy.
我这次该相信你么?
And I'm just supposed to trust you?
你脑子里全是一团糨糊 丑八怪
Cram it with walnuts,ugly.
这不是一场游戏  孩子
This isn't a game,son.
路西法的力量不是语言可以形容的
Lucifer is powerful in ways that defy description.
我们现在必须小心突击
We need to strike now,hard and fast --
在他发现他的皮囊之前
Before he finds his vessel.
他的皮囊?
His vessel?
路西法也需要肉身吗?
Lucifer needs a meat suit?
他是天使
He is an angel.
自然要按规矩办事
Them's the rules.
一旦他降临人间
And when he touches down,
天启四骑士 赤红的江河  炽热的天来临的日子
We're talking four horsemen,red oceans,fiery skies --
也离我们不远了
The greatest hits.
你可以阻止他  迪恩
You can stop him,Dean.
但你需要我们的帮助
But you need our help.
给我听着  你这个两面派的蠢驴
You listen to me,you two-faced douche --
看了你做的那些事之后  我就不会再指望你什么了
After what you did,I don't want jack squat from you!
你给我听着  小子
You listen to me,boy!
你要和我们作对吗
You think you can rebel against us?
象路西法那样吗
As Lucifer did?
你在流血
You're bleeding.
是啊
Oh,yeah.
以防万一你们这群家伙出现  我给自己买了个小保险
A little insurance policy in case you dicks showed up.
不
No!
是跟我朋友卡西学来的  你们这群狗娘养的家伙
Learned that from my friend Cass,you son of a bitch.
简直糟透了
This sucks ass.
给你
Here.
魔法袋  有了这个  那些天使就找不到我们
Hex bags. No way the angels will find us with those.
魔鬼也是
Demons,either,for that matter.
-在哪儿弄到的  - 我自己弄的
- Where'd you get it? - I made it.
怎么弄
How?
露比教我的
I... I learned it from Ruby.
说起这个
Speaking of...
你身体没什么状况吧
How you doing?
还有嗜血的欲望没  或是别的什么
Are you jonesing for another hit of bitch blood or what?
是很奇怪
I-it's weird.
但事实就是  我很好
Uh,tell you the truth,I'm fine.
不发抖  没发烧
No shakes,no fever.
好像是那个把我放进飞机里的人
It's like whoever...
顺便也给我治好了
Put me on that plane cleaned me right up.
超自然牌镇定剂
Supernatural methadone.
嗯  我想也是
Yeah,I guess.
-迪恩  - 萨姆
- Dean. - Sam.
没事了  你什么都不用说
It's okay. You don't have to say anything.
好吧
Well,that's good.
不然我能说什么
Because what can I even say?
对不起  我全搞砸了
"I'm sorry"? "I screwed up"?
那不是真的为了正义而战  你知道吗
Doesn't really do it justice,you know?
听着  我无话可说也无能为力
Look,there's nothing I can do or say
已经不能改变事实了
That will ever make this right --
那你何必要继续说下去呢
So why do you keep bringing it up?!
听着  我的意思是
Look,all I'm saying is,
我们为何不把事情看简单一点呢
Why do we have to put this under a microscope?
我们搞砸了  我们就收拾残局  就这样
We made a mess. We clean it up. That's it.
这只是另外一个驱魔行动而已
All right,so,say this is just any other hunt.
知道吗  我们现在该做什么
You know? What do we do first?
我们应该去找到那些东西
We'd,uh,figure out where the thing is.
很好
All right.
那我们就去找那些
So we just got to find...
恶魔
The devil.
(特拉华州  派克河)
不要怕
All right,keep it together.
不要怕  不要怕
Keep it together,man.
就是你 尼克
It's you,Nick.
你很特别
You're special.
你是被选中的人
You're chosen.
接着  萨姆抚摸
"And then Sam touched" --
不对
No.
爱抚着迪恩的锁骨
"Caressed Dean's clavicle.
不行  迪恩说
"'This is wrong,' said Dean.
我不管对错与否
"'Then I don't want to be right,'
萨姆用沙哑的声音回道
Replied Sam,in a husky voice."
我的天呐
Oh...my...god.
是你
You.
-你是  - 卡佛·爱德伦  你好贝基
- You're... - Carver Edlund,yeah. Hi,Becky.
你收到我的信了
You got my letters.
还有我的杏仁蛋白软糖
And my marzipan.
是的  是的  味道很好
Yeah,yeah. um...yummy.
不过
But,uh --
我是你的头号粉丝
I am your number-one fan.
你知道吗  我是舔舐萨姆81
You know,I'm Samlicker81.
不好意思  你是  你是什么
I'm sorry. You're -- you're what?
"不只是兄弟情"网站的女站长
Webmistress at morethanbrothers.net?
对  对  你是我的头号粉丝
Oh,yeah. no,yeah. you're my...number-one fan.
所以我才要找你
That's why I contacted you.
你是唯一信我的人
You're the only one who will believe me.
你还好吗
Are you all right?
不好
No.
我被监视了
I'm being watched.
不过至少现在应该没有
Okay,not now -- at least,I don't think so.
但我时间不多
But I don't have much time.
我需要你帮忙
I need your help.
你需要我的帮忙
You need my help?
是的
That's right.
你帮我捎信给萨姆和迪恩
I need you to get a message to Sam and Dean.
好吗
Okay?
听着  爱德伦先生
Look,mr. Edlund...
不错  我是你的粉丝
Yes,I'm a fan,
但我真不愿意被人嘲弄
But I really don't appreciate being mocked.
我只知道"凶鬼恶灵"是一本书而已  不是吗
I know that "supernatural's" just a book,okay?
我能区分现实和想象
I know the difference between fantasy and reality.
贝基 那些都是真的
Becky,it's all real.
我就知道
I knew it!
不过你能解释一下
But then how would you explain an earthquake,
为何地震  飓风和与日俱增的龙卷风
A hurricane,and multiple tornadoes,
会同时刻出现在地球吗
All at the same time,all around the globe?
三个字  碳排放
Two words -- carbon emissions.
是啊  波动凹凸
Yeah,right,wavy gravy.
女士  你没事吧
You okay,lady?
萨姆  真的是你吗
Sam...is it really you?
你长得真壮实
And you're so firm.
我认识你吗
Do I know you?
不认识  但我认识你
No. But I know you.
你是萨姆·温彻斯特
You're Sam Winchester.
你是
And you're...
跟我描写的不太一样
...not what I pictured.
我叫贝基
I'm Becky.
我读了关于你们所有的书
I read all about you guys.
我还写了一些...
And I've even written a few --
总之
Anyway...
爱德伦先生告诉我你们在这儿
Mr. Edlund told me where you were.
恰克?
Chuck?
他有事要转告  但他被监视了
He's got a message,but he's being watched.
是天使
Angels.
顺便说下  这个开场真不错
Nice change-up to the mythology,by the way.
那些魔鬼正在衰弱
The demon stuff was getting kind of old.
好  他要转告什么事
Right. just,um... what's the message?
他又看到幻象了
He had a vision.
天使落下米迦勒之剑于地球
"the michael sword is on earth. the angels lost it."
米迦勒之剑
The michael sword?
贝基  他知道剑在哪儿吗
Becky,does he know where it is?
在山岗上有42只看门狗把守的城堡里
In a castle,on a hill made of 42 dogs.
42只看门狗
42 dogs?
你确定没记错
Are...you sure you got that right?
听起来是挺荒谬  不过正是他所说的
It doesn't make sense,but that's what he said.
我记住了他说的每一个字
I memorized every word...
为你
For you.
贝基  能否请你不要再摸我了
Becky,c-- uh,can you...quit touching me?
不行
No.
嗨  鲍比
Hey,Bobby.
很高兴你们还安然无恙
Good to see you boys all in one piece.
没被跟踪吧
You weren't followed,were you?
被谁跟踪  天使
You mean by angels,
魔鬼还是超级萨迷
Demons,or Sam's new superfan?
你听说了
You heard.
是的  罗密欧
I heard,Romeo.
那么是米迦勒之剑  对吧
So... Sword of Michael,huh?
你认为我们所说的是
You think we're talking about the actual sword
在真实的天使长手中的真剑
From the actual archangel?
但愿如此吧
You better friggin' hope so.
这就是米迦勒  最强的天使混蛋
That's Michael ... toughest sumbitch they got.
开玩笑吧  强
You kidding me? tough?
他看上去像凯特·布兰切特
That guy looks like Cate Blanchett.
我不会想在昏暗的小道中遇上他  相信我
Well,I wouldn't want to meet him in a dark alley,believe me.
他指挥着天使们
He commands the heavenly host.
在最后的天使大战中
During the last big dust-up upstairs,
他把路西法赶进了地狱
He's the one who booted Lucifer's ass to the basement.
用的就是这把剑
Did it with that sword.
那如果我们能找到它的话
So if we can find it...
我们能再让他滚蛋
We can kick the devil's ass all over again.
好吧  那我们从哪入手
All right. So,where do we start?
先分头看书吧
Divvy up and start reading...
试着弄清楚恰克的胡言乱语
Try and make sense of chuck's nonsense.
孩子
Kid?
你还好吧
You all right?
不  不好
No,actually.
鲍比  这都是我的错  我很抱歉
Bobby,this is all my fault. I'm sorry.
萨姆
Sam...
莉莉丝没打破最后的封印
Lilith did not break the final seal.
她就是最后的封印
Lilith was the final seal.
萨姆  别说了
Sam,stop it.
我杀了她  是我把路西法放出来的
I killed her,and I set lucifer free.
什么
You what?!
你们叫我要小心提防露比
You guys warned me about Ruby,
别碰恶魔之学  但我不听
The demon blood,but I didn't listen.
是我把他放出来的
I brought this on.
真谢谢了你的不听话
You're damn right you didn't listen.
你冲动  自私  傲慢
You were reckless and selfish and arrogant.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
是吗
Oh,yeah?
内疚是你导致了这场世界存亡之战
You're sorry you started armageddon?
这件事情不能被原谅
This kind of thing don't get forgiven,boy.
如果我们最后能奇迹般的渡过难关
If,by some miracle,we pull this off...
我不想再见到你
I want you to lose my number.
明白了吗
You understand me?
附近有个旧教堂
There's an old church nearby.
也许我该去那里查查相关记载
Maybe I'll go read some of the lore books there.
不错
Yeah.
你去吧
You do that.
我没想到你父亲是对的
I never would have guessed that your daddy was right.
什么对了
About what?
关于你的弟弟
About your brother.
约翰说过
What John said
要么救萨姆  要么杀了他
You save sam or kill him.
也许
Maybe...
也许什么
Maybe what?
也许我们不该那么拼命的救他
Maybe we shouldn't have tried so hard to save him.
鲍比
Bobby.
他招来了世界末日  迪恩
He ended the world,Dean.
你和我都没能成功的阻止他
And you and I weren't strong enough to stop him proper.
这是我们的责任
That's on us.
你父亲是对的
Your dad's right.
爸爸
Dad.
应该是在这里
It's got to be in here somewhere.
你到底在说什么
What the hell are you talking about?
在这里
Here.
难以置信
I don't believe it.
这到底是什么
What the hell is it?
这是爸爸在纽约北部锁柜的卡片
It's a card for my Dad's lockup in upstate New York.
念念
Read it.
城堡储物  流浪山42号
"Castle storage. 42 rover hill."
是山上的一座城堡  那山上有42条狗
Castle on a hill of 42 dogs.
你认为你爸爸一直都保管着米迦勒之剑
So you think your Dad had the Michael Sword all this time?
不知道  我想先知就是这个意思
I don't know. I'm not sure what else Chuck could have meant.
是的
Yeah.
好吧
Okay.
对我来说  这真是个好消息
It's good enough for me.
我就知道你是个会无声无息
I always knew you were a big,dumb,slow,
慢慢扩散的伤口  迪恩
Dim pain in the ass,Dean.
但没想到你还是位贵客
But I never dreamt you were so v.i.p.
你想阻止路西法
I mean,you're gonna ice the devil?
就凭你
You?
我要知道的话
If I'd have known that,
早把你漂亮的脸蛋剥下来了
I'd have ripped your pretty,pretty face off ages ago.
露比
Ruby.
再猜猜  想想更早的时候
Try again. Go back further.
梅格
Meg?
你好
Hi.
迪恩  这是奇迹发生的时刻
These are the days of miracle and wonder,Dean.
父亲大人出现了
Our father's among us.
你知道  从我们还是人类的时候
You know we're all dreaming again
就这么盼望着
For the first time since we were human?
这是人间天堂
It's heaven on earth.
或人间地狱
Or hell.
我们欠你弟弟一个果篮
We really owe your brother a fruit basket.
老天  你太罗嗦了
My god,you like the sound of your own voice.
但你不同
But you,on the other hand,
你就像是马路上的障碍物
You're the only bump in the road.
每个恶魔  每一个
So every demon... every single one...
都想咬你一口
Is just dying for a piece of you.
先排队吧
Get in line.
我可排在前头哦  宝贝
Oh,I'm in the front of the line,baby.
让我们开始吧
Let's ride.
那是什么  花生黄油
What is that -- peanut butter?
你知道吗  你的代理老爸还醒着
You know,your surrogate daddy's still awake...
在身体里尖叫
Screaming in there.
我想让他感受下
And I want him to know how it feels
把你切成一片片的感觉
Slicing the life out of you.
鲍比
Bobby...
Bobby!
不
No!
现在
Now!
不
No!
你好  萨姆
Heya,sammy.
你想我吗  我是很想你
You miss me? 'Cause I sure missed you.
梅格
Meg?
没有了恶魔的超能力  不好受吧
It's not so easy without those super-special demon powers,
萨姆
Huh,Sammy?
不
No!
N-no!
不
No!
不  天啊  不
No,god,no!
我们需要帮助
Need some help here!
怎么了  他被刺伤了
What happened? he was stabbed.
推张床来
Can we get a gurney?
在这等着
Just wait here.
不  我们不能离开他
No,no,we ... we can't just leave him!
别走  我有问题要问
Just don't move. I've got questions.
-萨姆  我们得走了  - 不  不行  迪恩
- Sammy,we got to go. - No. No way,Dean.
恶魔们知道剑在哪里了
The demons heard where the sword is.
我们得赶在他们之前拿到剑
We got to get to it before they do,
如果还来得及的话
If we're not too late already.
走吧
Come on!
看来你们已经把剑的位置告诉恶魔了
I see you told the demons where the sword is.
感谢上帝  天使们来了
Oh,thank God. The angels are here.
想想看
And to think...
他们原本随时都可以拿到的
They could have grabbed it any time they wanted.
剑就在他们眼皮底下
It was right in front of them.
你什么意思
What do you mean?
恰克的这个预言或许是我们
We may have planted that particular piece of prophecy
有意放进他脑子里的  可它碰巧是真的
Inside Chuck's skull,but it happened to be true.
我们确实丢失了米迦勒之剑
We did lose the Michael Sword.
真的找不到了
We truly couldn't find it.
直到现在  你亲手把它交还给了我们
Until now. You've just hand-delivered it to us.
我们什么都没有
We don't have anything.
笨蛋  你就是
It's you,Chucklehead.
你是米迦勒之剑
You're the Michael Sword.
怎么  你真以为自己能杀死路西法
What... You thought you could actually kill Lucifer?
就凭你个自怨自艾强颜傻笑的惊弓之鸟
You simpering wad of insecurity and self-loathing?
不
No.
你只是个人类  迪恩
You're just a human,Dean.
还不完全是
And not much of one.
你说我是那把剑是什么意思
What do you mean,I'm the sword?
你是米迦勒的武器
You're Michael's weapon.
或者说  他的  容器
Or,rather,his...receptacle.
我是个皮囊
I'm a vessel?
你是皮囊
You're the vessel.
米迦勒的皮囊
Michael's vessel.
怎么可能  为什么  为什么是我
How? Why ... why me?
因为你命中注定
Because you're chosen!
这是荣誉  迪恩
It's a great honor,Dean.
是啊
Oh,yeah.
给天使做活套子
Yeah,life as an angel condom.
真有意思
That's real fun.
我还是不用了  多谢
I think I'll pass,thanks.
玩笑  又是玩笑
Joking. Always joking.
不开玩笑了
Well... no more jokes.
上帝
God!
狗娘养的
You son of a bitch!
你再骂  断的就不止是他的腿了
Keep mouthing off,I'll break more than his legs.
我受够了跟你浪费时间
I am completely and utterly through screwing around.
战争已经打响  我们的将军还没到
The war has begun. We don't have our general.
这样不好
That's bad.
现在  米迦勒会进入他的容器
Now,Michael is going to take his vessel
指挥消灭魔鬼的终结之战
And lead the final charge against the adversary.
你听懂了吗
You understand me?
混战会杀死多少人
How many humans die in the crossfire,huh?
一百万  五百万  一千万
A million? 5,10?
或许会更多
Probably more.
你知道如果不阻止路西法  会死多少人吗
If Lucifer goes unchecked,you know how many die?
所有人  他会把人间变成地狱
All of them. He'll roast the planet alive.
你不直接抓我  却跟我讲这些
There's a reason you're telling me this
一定是有原因的
Instead of just nabbing me.
你需要我的许可
You need my consent.
米迦勒需要我同意才能用我的身体
Michael needs my say-so to ride around in my skin.
很不幸  是的
Unfortunately,yes.
一定有还别的办法
Well,there's got to be another way.
没有别的办法
There is no other way.
仗一定要打
There must be a battle.
米迦勒必须战胜魔鬼
Michael must defeat the serpent.
经里写着的
It is written.
可能是吧
Yeah,maybe.
不过  话说回来
But,on the other hand...
去死
Eat me.
我不同意
The answer's no.
好吧
Okay.
这样如何
How about this?
你的朋友鲍比  他伤得很重
Your friend Bobby ... we know he's gravely injured.
你同意  我们就让他康复
Uh,say yes,and we'll heal him.
不同意  他就再也起不来了
Say no,he'll never walk again.
不
No.
如果我们治好你的
Then how about we heal you from...
晚期胃癌呢
Stage-4 stomach cancer?
不
No.
那就来点儿新鲜的
Then let's get really creative.
让我们看看  萨姆没了肺会怎么样
Uh,let's see how... Sam does without his lungs.
觉得好玩吗
Are we having fun yet?
你会同意的  迪恩
You're going to say yes,Dean.
杀了我们吧
Just kill us.
杀了你们
Kill you?
不
Oh,no.
我才刚刚开始
I'm just getting started.
你怎么会
How are you...
还活着
Alive?
问得好
That's a good question.
他们两个怎么会上了飞机
How did these two end up on that airplane?
也是个好问题
Another good question.
因为不是天使做的
'cause the angels didn't do it.
我想我们都知道答案  是吧
I think we both know the answer,don't we?
不
No.
不可能
That's not possible.
你害怕了
It scares you.
你应该害怕
Well,it should.
现在把他们俩治好  然后滚
Now,put these boys back together and go.
我不说第二次
I won't ask twice.
你们俩个要更加小心
You two need to be more careful.
是啊  我发现了
Yeah,I'm starting to get that.
你的兄弟比我预计得要混账
Your frat brothers are bigger dicks than I thought.
我说的不是天使
I don't mean the angels.
路西法正在接近他的皮囊
Lucifer is circling his vessel.
一旦他得手
And once he takes it,
巫毒袋就帮不了你们了
Those hex bags won't be enough to protect you.
这是什么鬼东西
What the hell was that?
以诺派印记
An Enochian Sigil.
它能让任何天使都无法发现你们
It'll hide you from every angel in creation,
包括路西法
Including Lucifer.
什么  你把那东西印在我们身上了
What,you just brand us with it?
不  我刻在你们肋骨上了
No. I carved it into your ribs.
卡西  你真的死了吗
Hey,Cass,were you really dead?
是的
Yes.
那你怎么回来的
Then how are you back?
尼克
Nick.
这是梦  尼克
You're dreaming,Nick.
但并不是说这不是真的
But it doesn't mean this isn't real.
莎拉
Sarah?
我不是你妻子  尼克
I'm not your wife,Nick.
我是天使
I'm an angel.
天使
An angel?
我叫路西法
My name is Lucifer.
当然
Sure.
这是自然
Naturally.
能帮我个忙吗  撒旦
Could you do me a favor there,Satan,
提醒我以后睡前别喝酒
And remind me to quit drinking before I go to bed?
我来是因为你很特别  尼克
I'm here because you're special,Nick.
像你这样的人非常非常少
There's very,very few people like you.
是吗
Is that so?
你是一个皮囊  一个完美而强大的皮囊
You're a vessel -- a very powerful vessel.
确切地说  那意味着什么呢
Meaning what,exactly?
我需要借用并支配你的身体和意识
I need to take control of your mind and your body.
老实说
To be honest...
对你而言可能非常难受
It'll probably be unpleasant for you.
但却不得不这样
But it is necessary.
够了  听着
Okay,look...
为了你我好  我想还是立马醒来得好
If it's just the same to you,I think I'd like to wake up now.
我说过了  这是真的
I told you -- this is real.
不用害怕
Don't be afraid.
一切都取决于你
This is your choice.
得由你来邀请我
You need to invite me in.
即使是真的
Even if this is real --
就算是假的  也先假设是真的
Which it's not,but assuming it was --
我又凭什么要答应做这种事儿呢
Why the hell would I do something like that?
你们人类完全误会我了
You people misunderstand me.
你们称我为撒旦为魔鬼  但
You call me "Satan" and "Devil," but...
但你们真得了解我的罪孽吗
Do you know my crime?
我曾经那么深爱着上帝
I loved God too much.
尽管如此  他还是遗弃了我
And for that,he betrayed me --
并惩罚我
Punished me.
就像他惩罚你那样
Just as he's punished you.
否则  上帝怎么能眼睁睁地
After all,how could god stand idly by
那家伙闯入你家还将你的妻小
While that man broke into your home
血溅于床而袖手旁观呢
And butchered your family in their beds?
只有两种解释  尼克
There are only two rational answers,Nick
要么是他本就残暴嗜血
Either he's sadistic...
要么就是他压根就漠不关心
Or he simply doesn't care.
你很愤怒
You're angry.
你绝对有理由愤怒
You have every right to be angry.
我也很愤怒
I am angry,too.
所以我才想要把他找出来
That's why I want to find him
让他对这一切交代清楚
Hold him accountable for his actions.
不能因为他创造了我们
Just because he created us
我们就该让他随意愚弄  任他鱼肉
Doesn't mean he can toy with us,like playthings.
如果我帮了你
If I help you...
你能让我的家人回到我身边吗
Can you bring back my family?
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我办不到
I can't.
但我能给你其他更好的东西
But I can give you the next best thing.
上帝如此待你  尼克
God did this to you,Nick.
而我能还你公道
And I can give you justice.
还你安宁
Peace.
我怎么知道你现在所说的是真的呢
How do I know you're telling the truth?
因为  和你们所知的恰恰相反
Because,contrary to popular belief,
我不会说谎
I don't lie.
更不需要说谎
I don't need to.
我需要的
What I need...
就是你
Is you.
尼克  我需要你说声同意
Nick,I need you to say yes.
那么  我同意
Then yes.
什么叫可能再无法行走了
"Unlikely to walk again"?
为什么啊  你这嘴上无毛的二愣子
Why,you snot-nosed son of a bitch!
等我下了这床
Wait till I get out of this bed!
看我不用这条瘸腿踢爆你的屁屁
I'll use my game leg and kick your friggin' ass!
对啊  最好能跑快点儿
Yeah,you better run!
你们信那蠢货的话吗
You believe that yahoo?
由他去吧  你绝对会好起来的
Screw him. you'll be fine.
不过  让我问个超级重要的问题先
So,let me ask the million-dollar question.
我们现在该怎么办
What do we do now?
我想  就只能尽最大努力能救多少是多少了
We save as many as we can for as long as we can,I guess.
虽然那根本就是垂死挣扎
It's bad.
管他是天堂还是地狱赢了  我们都是垫背的
Whoever wins,heaven or hell,we're boned.
那如果是我们赢了呢
What if we win?
我是说真的
I'm serious.
管他天使还是恶魔
I mean,screw the angels and the demons
还有他们那个狗屁天启都滚一边儿去
And their crap apocalypse.
他们想火拼开战  找别地儿去
They want to fight a war,they can find their own planet.
这儿可是我们的地盘  绝不让他们在这儿随便撒野
This one's ours,and I say they get the hell off it.
我们就跟他们来硬的  遇魔杀魔
We take 'em all on. we kill the devil.
如有必要杀了米迦勒也在所不惜
Hell,we even kill Michael if we have to.
但这一切都得由我们自己做主
But we do it our own damn selves.
那我们要怎么办到这一切呢  我的天才
And how are we supposed to do all this,genius?
我还没头绪呢
I got no idea.
但就我个人而言  我已经万事俱备了
But what I do have is a g.e.d.
只需要来一阵东风  我就能直捣皇穴了
And a "give 'em hell" attitude,and I'll figure it out.
小子  你果真是个冲动的单细胞生物
You are nine kinds of crazy,boy.
早听你们说过了
It's been said.
听着  你呆这儿好好养伤
Listen,you stay on the mend.
我们迟些再来看你
We'll see you in a bit.
萨姆
Sam?
我当时是清醒的
I was awake.
我很清楚自己说过什么
I know what I said back there.
我只想告诉你
I just want you to know that...
那些话并非我本意
That was the demon talking.
我决不会弃你于不顾  孩子
I ain't cutting you out,boy.
永远都不会
Not ever.
谢谢你  鲍比
Thanks,Bobby.
别客气
You're welcome.
我这次负伤应得勋章奖励的
I deserve a damn medal for this,
不过  别客气
But...you're welcome.
我在想  迪恩
You know,I was thinking,Dean
也许我们可以再重造柯尔特枪
Maybe we could go after The Colt.
为什么  重造它有什么特别吗
Why? what difference would that make?
我们可以用它来对付路西法
Well,we could use it on Lucifer.
你刚刚不也说了要回来吗
I mean,you just said back there --
我刚刚那堆废话只是宽慰鲍比而已
I just said a bunch of crap for Bobby's benefit.
我是说  我会奋战
I mean... I'll fight.
我一定会奋战到最后一刻  但坦白而言
I'll fight till the last man,but let's at least be honest.
我们压根就没有任何机会
I mean,we don't stand a snowball's chance,
你心知肚明
And you know that.
该死的  你们大家都心知肚明得很
I mean,hell,you of all people know that.
迪恩
Dean...
你是不是有话想对我说
Is there something you want to say to me?
我努力试过了  萨姆
I tried,Sammy.
我真得努力尝试过了
I mean,I really tried.
但我真得无法再继续假装一切如初
But I just can't keep pretending that everything's all right.
因为已经无法如初了
Because it's not.
已经再也回不去了
And it's never going to be.
你竟然选择了恶魔而不是我
You chose a demon over your own brother,
接下来瞧瞧着发生的一切
And look what happened.
我愿意用任何  任何东西
I would give anything -- anything --
来弥补发生的一切
To take it all back.
我知道你愿意
I know you would.
更知道你有多后悔多愧疚  我很清楚
And I know how sorry you are. I do.
但  我的老弟
But,man...
你曾是我唯一的最信任的依靠
You were the one that I depended on the most.
然而你让我心寒的方式是我从没有..
And you let me down in ways that I can't even...
我只是
I'm just --
要我现在就忘记并原谅你实在有点儿难
I'm having a hard time forgiving and forgetting here.
明白吗
You know?
我要怎么去弥补呢
What can I do?
想听真话吗
Honestly?
没法弥补
Nothing.
我只是没办法
I just don't...
我想我们已经无法回到以前了
I don't think that we can ever be what we were.
懂吗
You know?
我已经无法再信任你了
I just don't think I can trust you.